Guide to the Wendell Ricketts papers, circa 1961-2004.
Ricketts, Wendell papers, circa 1961-2004.
- Series VI. Audiovisual Materials
  - Photographs
    - Italian gay event, April 1994; [oversize photograph] (Box 13, Folder 4)
Bandiera Gay: Il movimento gay in Italia dalle origini al 2000 attraverso l'Archivio Massimo Consoli. Edizioni Libreria Croce, 1999.
Barrus, Emery. The AIDS Conspiracy. Santa Barbara: Fithian Press, 1988.
Bay Area Reporter. v.22:no.25 (1992:June 25); v.23:no.22, 25 (1993:June 3, 24)
Beta: bulletin of experimental treatments for AIDS: a publication of the San Francisco AIDS Foundation. 1991:May,Aug.,Nov.; 1992:Feb.,May; 1994:June,Sep.; 1995: Mar.,Sep.,Oct.; 1996: June
Beta: boletin de tratamientos experimentales para el SIDA: edicion en espanol. 1993:Sep.; 1994:Sep.
Bieber, Irving, et. al. Homosexuality: A Psychoanalytic Study. Northvale, NJ: Aronson, 1988.
The Black Scholar: Blacks & the Sexual Revolution. Apr. 1978.
Blair, Ralph. Etiological and Treatment Literature on Homosexuality, 1972.
Bloch, Iwan. Die Prostitution. Nerlin, 1925.
Bloch, Iwan. Strange Sexual Practises in all Races of the World. New York: Falstaff Press, Inc., 1933.
Blue Mesa Review: Love & Sex in the 21st Century. Albuquerque, NM: University of New Mexico. No. 10 (1998). (includes story by Wendell Ricketts, beginning p. 15)
Boswell, John. Alla Scoperta dell'Amore: Archetipi di Amore Gay nella Storia Cristiana, con un saggio di Massimo Consoli. Rome: Edizioni Libreria Croce, 1982.
Bright, Deborah (ed). The Passionate Camera: Photography and Bodies of Desire. London: Routledge, 1998.
Bronski, Michael. Culture Clash: The Making of Gay Sensibility. Boston, MA: South End Press, 1984.
Butterfield, Oliver. Marriage and Sexual Harmony. New York: Emerson Books, 1945.
Califia, Pat. The Advocate Adviser. Boston: Alyson Publications, Inc., 1991.
Califia, Pat. Diesel Fuel: Passionate Poetry. New York: Masquerade Books, 1997.
Califia, Pat, ed. Doing it for Daddy. Boston: Alyson Publications, Inc., 1994. (includes a story by Wendell Ricketts, beginning p. 135.)
Califia, Pat (ed). The Lesbian S/M Safety Manual. Denver, CO: Lace Publications, 1988.
Califia, Pat. Sapphistry: The Book of Lesbian Sexuality. Naiad Press, 1980.
California. 1983: July. (article on AIDS)
California Journal. 1975: Oct., 1979: Feb.
California Lawyer. 1992: Sept., 1994:June. (June issue contains article on lifting the military ban on gays)
Carter, Nicholas. Routine Circumcision: The Tragic Myth. London: Londinium Press, 1979.
Cauldwell, D.O. The Intimate Embrace: Some uncommon facts about a natural function. Girard, Kansas: Haldeman-Julius, 1949.
Caulfield, Charles. The Anarchis AIDS Medical Formulary: A Guide to Guerrilla Immunology. Berkeley: North Atlantic Books, 1993.
Chin, Justin. Bite Hard. San Francisco: Manic D Press, 1997.
Christopher Street. Vol. 3, No. 6-Vol. 4, No. 4; Vol. 8, No. 7-Vol. 11, No. 3; Vol. 11, No. 5-Vol. 13, No 5; Vol. 14, No. 24.
Ciao! A Newsletter Dedicated to Examing the Comics Industry's Awareness of Issues #5: June 1992.
College English: The Official Journal of the National Council of Teachers of English. V.35 no.6: Mar.1974.
Coming to Power. Boston: Alyson Publications, 1987.
Crisp, Quentin. How To Go To the Movies. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1989.
Crossroads: Contemporary Political Analysis & Left Dialogue. Nov. 1991, no.15 (Article: Queer Relations: The Lesbian/Gay Movement & the US Left)
De Jim, Strange. The Strange Experience. San Francisco :Ash-Kar Press, 1980.
Detainer (fetish-wear catalogue), London, UK.
Directory of HIV Clinical Trials in the Bay Area. 1992:summer; 1993:summer; 1993/1994:winter; 1994:summer
Directory of HIV Clinical Trials in the Bay Area and Northern California. 1995:fall
Dolce Roma, guida all'incontro Rome: Robin Edizioni, 1991.
Echo. The magazine of the southwest. v.8:no.4 (1996:Oct.31)
Ellmann, Richard. Oscar Wilde. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1988.
Everything that Has Been Shall Be Again: The Reincarnation Fables of John Gilgun. St. Paul, MN: Bieler Press, 1981.
Family Limitation. (information pamphlet)
Final report: "strengthening families, a model for community action." By Thomas F Coleman; Los Angeles (Calif.). Task Force on Family Diversity.; National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (U.S.)
The Front Page. v.12:no.13 (1991:July16)
The Gay Book. San Francisco. 7th ed., Summer/Fall 1988.
Gay Comix. No.1-4.6,8-12,14,18,19.
Gay Information. No. 6. Winter 1981
Gay Insurgent. No. 7, 1981.
Gaybeat. v.9:no.2 (1993:Feb.)
Gerbil.Nos. 7, 8.
Gidlow, Elsa. Ask No Man Pardon: The Philosophical Significance of Being Lesbian. Mill Valley, CA: Druid Heights Books, 1975.
Gilgun, John. From the Inside Out. Mulvane, KS: Three Phase Publishing, 1991.
Gomez, Jewelle L. Flamingoes & Bears. Jersey City, NJ: Grace Publications, 1986.
Gonzalez, Rigoberto. So Often the Pitcher Goes to Water until It Breaks. Chicago: University of Illinois Press, 1999.
Guibert, Hervé. The Compassion Protocol. James Kirkup, tr. New York: George Braziller, Inc., 1994.
Harris, Paul (ed). The Queer Press Guide 2000. New York: Painted Leaf Press, 1999.
Hawaii Observer. No.110: Aug. 28, 1977. (article: Local Gays: The Boys in the Bars)
The Heartlands Today. Huron, OH: The Firelands Writing Center, 2000.
Henkin, William and Sybil Holiday. Consensual Sadomasochism. San Francisco: Daedalus Publishing Co., 1996.
Hockney, David. 72 Drawings. New York: The Viking Press, Inc., 1971.
Hothead Paisan: Homicidal Lesbian Terrorist. No.1-5,7,9-10.
Hustler: a story in photo of a young man's search for himself. Published by Mark IV enterprises, inc. 1969.
In: A Golden Boys Presentation. V.1 no.1.
In Step. v.8:issue 15,17 (1991:Aug.1/14, Aug.29/Sep.11)
Island Lifestyle. September 1991.
Journal of Social Work & Human Sexuality. Vol. 5, No. 1 (includes article by Wendell Ricketts, starting p.35), Vol. 5, No. 2 (introduction co-authored by Wendell Ricketts).
Kinnard, Rupert. B.B. and the Diva. Boston: Alyson Publications, 1992.
The Ladder. July, August, September 1966.
Lauritsen, John & Ian Young. The AIDS Cult: Essays on the Gay Health Crisis. Provincetown: Asklepios, 1997.
A lesbian and gay parents' legal guide to child custody. Published by the Anti-Sexism Committee of the San Francisco-Bay Area Chapter of the National Lawyers' Guild, 1985.
Liberation and Marxism. No.17: spring 1993.
Long, H.W. Sane Sex Life and Sane Sex Living. Boston: Gorham Press, 1919.
Markman, Ronald, M.D. and Dominick Bosco. Alone with the Devil: Famous Cases of a Courtroom Psychiatrist. New York: Bantam Books, 1990. (Ch. 4, "Cold-Blooded Heat of Passion," discusses (pseudonymously) the case of Robert Rosenkrantz.)
Martin, April. The Lesbian and Gay Parenting Handbook. New York: Haworth Medical Press,1993.
McCall's. v.105 no.6, Mar. 1978. (article: The truth about homosexual teachers)
McNeill, John. The Church and the Homosexual. Kansas City: Sheed Andrews and McMeel Inc., 1976.
Mercer, Jessie Decamarron. They Walk in Shadow: A Study of Sexual Variations With Emphasis on the Ambisexual and Homosexual Components and Our Contemporary Sex Laws, New York: Comet Press Books, Reflection Books, 1959. (signed by author)
Metroline. Vol. 14, No. 6-9, 15, 17-18 (1991).
Modern Adonis. No.36.
Naughty Bits. Nos.6-7.
New Mexico Rainbow. v.4:issue 7,9 (1997:Apr18, May16)
New York. June 25, 1979. (article on gays).
Newsweek. June 6,1977. (article: Battle over Gay Rights: Anita Bryant vs. The Homosexuals)
Nicholls, Mark. The Importance of Being Oscar: The Life & Wit of Oscar Wilde. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1980.
The Normal Heart. The newsletter of the lesbian and gay community of Southern New Mexico. v.7: no.5 (1996: Sep./Oct.)
Ortleb, Charles and Richard Fiala. Relax! This Book is Only a Phase You're Going Through!. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1978.
Our Working Lives. Huron, OH: Bottom Dog Press, 2000.
Out! magazine. 1997: June.
Pauling, Linus, et.al. Stop the FDA: Save your Health Freedom. Menlo Park, CA: Health Freedom Publications, 1992.
Positive News. Summer 1994.
Preston, John. Mr. Benson. New York: Masquerade Books, Inc., 1992.
Preston, John. My Life as a Pornographer. New York: Masquerade Books, Inc., 1993.
Richmond, Len and Gary Noguera. The Gay Liberation Book. San Francisco: Ramparts Press, 1973.
Ricketts, Wendell. Brownian Movement: A Journal of 15 Nights in the Land of Enchantment. San Francisco, 1996.
Ricketts, Wendell. Lesbians and Gay Men as Foster Parents. Portland, ME: National Child Welfare Resource Center, 1991.
Saffron, Lisa. 'What About the Children?'. New York: Cassell, 1996.
San Francisco Bay Times. v.15:no.34 (1995:Jan.27)
San Francisco Sentinel. v.20:no.26 (1992:June 25); v.21:no.15,21,25,32 (1993:Apr.15, May 26, June 23, Aug. 11)
Schlafly, Phyllis. A Choice Not an Echo. Alton, Ill.: Pere Marquette Press, 1964.
Sedgwick, Eve Kosofsky. Epistemology of the Closet. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1990.
Sexual Behavior. v.1:no.2,4,9 (1971:May,July,Dec.); v.2:no.5,7 (1972:May,July)
Sherrill, Jan-Mitchell. Friend of the Groom. Baltimore, MD: New Poets Series, Inc., 1993.
Shilts, Randy. The Mayor of Castro Street: The Life & Times of Harvey Milk. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1982.
SIDA ahora. 1994/1995:invierno.
Stadler, Matthew. Allan Stein. New York: Grove Press, 1999.
Stearn, Jess. The Sixth Man. London: W.H. Allen, 1962.
Stonewall Union Reports. v.4,no.2 (1993:Mar.); v.5,no.1 (1993:Feb.)
Stopes, Marie Carmichael. Marrie Love: A new Contribution to the Solution of Sex Difficulties. London: G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1927.
Tales of the Closet. No.1-4.
Terman, Lewis M. Kinsey's "Sexual Behavior in the Human Male": Some Comments and Criticisms. Stanford: Psychological Bulletin, 1948.
Tribe: An American Gay Journal. Spring/Summer 1991.
Thompson, Mark. Gay Spirit: Myth and Meaning. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1987.
Thompson, Mark (ed). Leatherfolk: Radical Sex, People, Politics, and Practice. Boston: Alyson Publications, 1991.
Various Authors. The Modern Sex Book. [n.l.]: Haldeman-Julius Company: 1936.
Venus Infers. V.1 no.1-v.1 no.3, v.2 no.1.
Von Urban, Rudolf. Sex Perfection and Marital Happiness. New York: Dial Press, 1949.
Watch Out Comix. No.1.
Weber, Bruce (photographer). Calvin Klein Jeans.
White, Marvin K. Last Rights. Los Angeles: Alyson Publications, 1999.
The Wisconsin Light. v.4:no.17-18 (1991:Aug.8/21,Aug.22/Sep.4)
The Young Physique. v.2:no.2 (1960:June); v.4:no.5 (1963:Jan.); v.5:no.1 (1963:May)